"生活大爆炸" 前情提要...
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
当时有个女孩
Well, there was this girl.
你干嘛了?
What did you do?
没什么大事
Nothing.
真的 就亲了一下
Really, it was just kissing.
好吧
All right.
那 我们还是要结婚的吧?
So, we're still getting married?
是啊
Yes.
因为我们彼此相爱
Because we love each other.
是啊
Yes.
而且这是我们最开心的一天
And it's the happiest day of our life.
别得寸进尺
Don't push it.
我需要一点时间
I need some time to take a step back
重新考虑一下我们的关系
and reevaluate our situation.
哦
Oh.
再见 Sheldon
Bye, Sheldon.
咕噜...
Well, Gollum...
你最懂戒指了
you're an expert on rings.
那我该拿这个戒指怎么办呢?
What do I do with this one?
现在...
你想要哪个套餐?
So, what package are you thinking?
这套里面包括了音乐和鲜花
Mm, this one comes with music and flowers.
他们还会把整个视频传到网上
Oh, they even stream the whole thing live on the Internet.
干嘛要传网上?
Why would we want that?
因为有很多漂亮的金发妞
'Cause there's a lot of gorgeous blondes out there
不相信自己会嫁一个又矮又近视的科学家
who don't believe they can land a short, nearsighted scientist.
我们传播点希望吧
Let's give them hope.
随便啦 就传到网上吧
Whatever. Put us on the Internet.
反正我一直想给婚礼加个评论区
I've always wanted a wedding with a comment section.
我... 如果你不喜欢 我们可以先不结婚
I... If you're not into this, we can do it another time.
不不 我想结婚
No. No, I want to.
听着 我们已经拖得够久了
Look, we've put this off long enough.
来吧
Let's do it.
我们第一次滚床单的时候你也这么说
That's exactly what you said the first time we slept together.
抱歉
Oh, excuse me.
是Sheldon
Sheldon.
嘿
Hey.
Leonard 你结婚了吗?
Leonard, have you gotten married yet?
没 干嘛这么问?
No. Why?
- 很好 别结!  - 为什么?
- Good. Don't do it!  - Why not?
我发现了非常重要的情报
Some important new information has come to light.
女人最渣了
Women are the worst.
我以为最疼不过被纸割伤 但我错了
I thought it was paper cuts, but I was wrong.
没有纸能伤我这么深
No piece of paper ever cut me this deep.
出什么事了?
What happened now?
Amy和我分手了
Amy has ended our relationship.
不 真的吗?
Oh, no. Seriously?
出什么事了?
What's going on?
Amy和Sheldon提分手了
Amy broke up with Sheldon.
她提了?
She did?
Penny哭了吗?
Is Penny crying?
没
No.
好吧 当然没有
No, of course not.
她们的快乐建立在我们痛苦之上
They thrive on our suffering.
兄弟... 我很难过
Buddy, I... I'm so sorry.
有什么我能做的?
Is there anything I can do?
有 如果我以后
Yes. If I ever talk about
再说要和女孩子去约会 记得翻白眼
going out with a girl again, roll your eyes at me
就跟你干蠢事 我翻你白眼一样
like I do to you when you say dumb things.
Sheldon 好吧 虽然
Sheldon, uh, o-okay, just because
你和Amy的事情不顺利
you're going through this with Amy
并不意味着所有女人都渣
doesn't mean that all women are bad.
随便了
Whatever.
我才听说
Hey, I just heard
你和Sheldon的事 你还好吗?
about you and Sheldon. Are you okay?
不太好
Not really.
你能过来一下吗?
Can you come over?
嗯 其实我现在在拉斯维加斯
Uh, actually I'm in Vegas.
Leonard和我就要结婚了
Leonard and I are about to get married.
等等
Hold on.
你们结婚居然不邀请我?
You're getting married and you didn't invite me?
我们只是一时兴起
Well, it was kind of a spur-of-the-moment thing.
哇
Wow.
希望我可以在这接到你扔来的花
Hope I can catch the bouquet from here.
Amy 不要这样
Amy, don't be like that.
为什么我听到了Amy的名字?
Why did I just hear Amy's name?
Penny正和她打电话呢
Penny's on the phone with her.
她说我什么了吗?
Did she say anything about me?
没事了 我才不关心呢
Never mind. I don't care.
如果你关心的话你可以告诉我她说了什么
Well, if you care, you can find out and tell me.
当你发现我其实并不关心这些时不要吃惊
Just don't be shocked when you find out that I don't care.
你能不能别这么激动?
Okay, will you relax?
这又不是什么大不了的事
You're not missing anything special.
说什么呢?
Hey?
她很不开心
She's upset.
婚礼将会非常好的
Look, it's gonna be a great wedding.
看你那穿着西服的小样
Look at you in your little suit.
Amy不开心? 是因为我吗?
Amy's upset? Is it about me?
不是 我觉得是因为我们婚礼没邀请她
No, I think it's because we're eloping.
是因为你们的婚礼让她难受吗?
Your marriage is causing her pain?
太棒了 我收回刚才的话
Yeah, great, I take it back.
结吧! 为爱狂欢!
Go ahead and do it. Yay for love!
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆炸了... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool,Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History,unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第1集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 凤梨酥  时间轴: 奥利奥
校对: Uriana
翻译: 酱油影 肉肉君 凤梨酥
猫呗 柱子君 奥利奥 波特妹子
- 你好  - 天哪!
- Hello.  - Oh!
你在这干嘛?
What are you doing here?
我们上一次交谈 你说你需要时间
When last we spoke, you said you needed time.
才11个小时啊!
Well, it's only been 11 hours!
指环王三部曲也差不多是11个小时
The Lord of the Rings trilogy was nearly 11 hours.
我逼你看了它 你说简直比一辈子还长
I made you watch that, you said it was an eternity.
Sheldon 当我准备好时我会告诉你的
Sheldon, when I'm ready to talk, I'll let you know.
好吧
Very well.
你好像要去什么地方
You seem to be headed somewhere.
我可以和你一起去吗?
May I walk with you?
当然
Sure.
天哪 真高兴我们又可以一起去约会了
Boy, I'm glad we're going out again.
我们已经不在一起了
We're not back together.
为什么?
Why?
你看上别人了吗?
Is there someone else?
等不及跟别人上床了
Just couldn't wait for that first notch on your bedpost
是吗?
could you?
如果你一定想知道的话
If you must know,
我要去Howard家
I'm going to Howard and Bernadette's
看婚礼
to watch the wedding.
那你要带哪个男的去?
And who's this guy you're taking?
根本就没有男的好吗!
There's no guy!
你要一个人去看婚礼吗?
Oh, you're going to a wedding alone?
太悲剧了
That's sad.
我才不孤单呢
I'm not gonna be alone.
你要是饿了的话 旁边的脱衣舞厅有
Hey, if you're hungry, there's a breakfast buffet
自助早餐
at the strip club next door.
谢了 不过我不太想吃洒着闪光粉的炒鸡蛋
Thanks, but I don't like glitter on my scrambled eggs.
应该不是脱衣舞娘做的早餐吧 不过无所谓啦
I don't think the strippers prepare the meal, but okay.
那个... 现在这样和我预想的也不太一样
Look, it... it's not how I pictured it either,
不过我还是很高兴我们真的要结婚了
but I'm still glad we're doing it.
- 我也是  - 真的吗?
- Me, too.  - You sure?
- 真的  - 那你能保证
- Yes.  - And you promise
对刚才车上我说的事完全不介意吗?
you're okay with everything from the car?
天啊 你能不能别提了?
Oh, my God, would you stop bringing it up?
你说得对 抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
我们有后半辈子的时间
We have the rest of our lives
为过去的事纠缠不休呢
to dredge stuff up from the past and fight about it.
所以 你说呢?
So what do you think?
我们要不要去旁边吃点东西?
Should we run next door and grab a bite?
要是一会叫到我们了怎么办?
What if they call our names?
没关系 他们给我这个震动号牌了
Oh, don't worry. They gave me this vibrating coaster.
还真是跟童话一样美好啊
Oh, and the fairy tale continues.
谢谢你们
Thank you for doing this.
不用谢
Our pleasure.
你感觉好点吗?
You feeling okay?
我们在一起的时间太长了
We were together for so long,
说实话 我自己都不知道现在是什么感觉
I honestly don't know what I'm feeling.
我深表理解
Well, that's understandable.
你忘了 这种感觉就是"快乐"
You forgot. It's called "Happy."
Howard你说什么呢
Howard.
我又没说什么不好的话
I'm not saying anything bad.
只不过是她爱上了束缚住她的人
Just that she was in love with her captor
而现在终于从他黑暗变态的地牢里逃出来了而已
and somehow managed to escape from his dark and crazy dungeon.
我明白你的感受
I know what you're going through.
我... 我上一次分手的时候也很难过
My... my last breakup was pretty tough.
你前女友叫什么?
Oh. What was her name?
嘿 我说的是真的
Hey, it's a true story.
别这样审问我
I don't need the third degree.
神啊 Sheldon 你在这里干什么呢?
For God's sake, Sheldon, what are you doing?
我没想进去
I didn't want to come in.
有人告诉我 如果我进去的话大家都会觉得不舒服
I was told it would make everyone feel uncomfortable.
所以我就在这里待着好了
So I'll just stay out here
还要假装没有很想去洗手间的样子
and pretend that I don't have to go to the bathroom.
Howard 交给你了
Howard, do something.
来了
I'm on it.
Sheldon 出现在这对你没好处啊
Sheldon, you being here might not be making things better.
我发现了
I see.
所以你们才邀请了除了我以外的所有人吗?
And is that why everybody was invited but me?
他们没有邀请除了你以外的所有人
They didn't invite everybody but you.
Bernadette邀请了我而已
Bernadette invited me,
Stuart就住在这里
and Stuart lives here.
谁想吃刚出炉的肉桂卷?
Who wants hot cinnamon rolls?
所以 一会听到的音乐就是你们的提示
So, when you hear the music, that's your cue.
还有什么问题吗?
Any questions?
呃 我们购买的套装里
Oh, the package that we paid for
好像还应该包括地毯上铺满玫瑰花瓣的
said the aisle was supposed to be strewn with rose petals.
玫瑰花瓣怎么没有了?!
Where are the rose petals?!
- 花瓣用完了!  - 这样啊
- We're out!  - You know what?
那算了吧
It's fine.
不过我们可以用洗手间里的干花!
We can use the potpourri from the bathroom!
真的 这样就行了
Really, we're good.
没错 就是想结个婚而已
Yup, just want to get married.
- 是的  - 好吧
- Yeah.  - Great.
我在前面等你们
I'll see you two up there.
- 就是现在了  - 是啊
- This is it.  - I know.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你们还要不要厕所的干花了?!
Was that a yes or no on the potpourri?!
- 不用 谢谢!  - 没事了!
- No, thank you!  - We're good!
Raj 你可能在好奇
Raj, you're probably wondering
为什么Amy和我没有在互诉情肠
why Amy and I aren't showing any affection to one another.
还没挤进我的好奇榜前十
Didn't even crack the top ten.
是这样的
Well, you should know
她刚刚和我分手了
that she recently broke up with me.
我说了我需要时间来考虑
I said I needed time to think.
你俩一定能想出些办法的
I'm sure you guys will figure something out.
你瞅瞅 Raj都崩溃了
You hear that? Raj is devastated.
Sheldon 嘘 婚礼开始了
Sheldon, shh. The wedding's starting.
我知道怎么回事了
I see what's happening.
大家要分裂成小团体了
Sides are forming.
假如Bernadette站在Amy那边 那我就选Howard
Well, if Bernadette's on Amy's team, I pick Howard.
我保持中立
I'm not taking sides.
好吧 那我只好选Raj了
Fine, I guess I'm stuck with Raj.
是吗?
Really?
至少有人选你呢
At least you got picked.
我提前问一句
Before I go any further,
你们双方都准备好婚礼誓词了吗?
have either of you prepared your own vows?
- 准备了  - 没有
- Yes.  - No.
你写了誓词?
You wrote vows?
对啊
Yeah.
我还没有呢
Well, I don't have any.
你这是让我出洋相啊
You're kind of making me look bad.
没事的 我... 我也没必要念出来
It's okay. I... I don't have to say them.
不 不 不 念吧
No, no, no, go ahead.
我能想点煽情的 然后你会哭 一切都搞定
I'll come up with something mushy, you'll cry, we got this.
"Penny 我们是由
"Penny, we are made of particles
"宇宙形成时就存在的粒子组成的
"That have existed since the moment the universe began.
"我相信这些原子
"I like to think those atoms traveled
"为了创造我们 穿越了140亿年的时空
"14 billion years through time and space to create us,
让我们相知相爱 让我们成为一体"
so that we could be together and make each other whole."
哇
Wow.
Penny你的呢?
Penny?
哦 对 嗯... 好吧
Right. Um... okay.
Leonard 你不只是我一生所爱
Leonard, I mean, you're not only the love of my life.
你还是我的挚友 而且...
I mean, you're my best friend, and...
我是你的好朋友
you've got a friend in me.
你遇到的困难
You got troubles.
也是我的困难
I got 'em, too.
我什么事都愿意为你做
There isn't anything I wouldn't do for you.
我们会齐心协力 然后解决问题
We stick together, and we can see it through,
因为... 我是你的好朋友
'cause... you've got a friend in me.
那是玩具总动员的主题曲吗?
Is that the song from Toy Story?
他超爱那部电影
He loves that movie.
的确
I do.
- 哇 这场面太美了  - 对啊
- Aw, that was beautiful.  - Yeah.
我是说 虽然不如咱们的婚礼美
I mean, not like our wedding beautiful.
不 我们赢定了
No, we totally won.
Amy 我不理解 我们到底有没有分手?
Amy, I don't understand, are we broken up or not?
好像你下不了决心一样
It's like you can't make up your mind.
因为你没有给我空间去考虑
It's because you're not giving me any space to think.
那你就给我快点儿想
Well, you should think fast,
因为男人一生都可以产生精子繁衍后代
because men can sire offspring their entire lives,
而你们的那些卵子就过期不候了
but those eggs you're toting around have a sell-by date.
Sheldon 你说出这种话让我不纠结了
You know what, Sheldon, you've made this really easy.
你幼稚 自私 刚才还当面侮辱我
You're immature, you're selfish, you just insulted me to my face.
我不需要再考虑了 我们分手了
I don't need any more time to think. We're broken up.
喂 Amy...
Amy...
有人载我回家吗?
Will someone take me home?
好吧 走吧 我带你回去
Yeah. Come on, I'll give you a ride.
象征了你们不朽的爱情
Symbolizes your eternal love.
我现在宣布你们结为夫妻
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
我们结婚啦!
We did it!
我真高兴你们能见证这一时刻!
I'm so glad you guys could watch!
我们在评论区里写上"甚是美好"吧
We'll say it was beautiful in the comment section.
不 不 不 等一会
No, no, no. Hang on.
新浪该抱着新娘跨过门槛的
I believe I'm supposed to carry you across the threshold.
你行吗你?
Can you?
你觉得每次Sheldon在电视机前睡着了
Who do you think carries Sheldon to bed
是谁把他抱上床睡觉的?
when he falls asleep in front of the TV?
好吧 那你抱吧
Okay, let's do it.
- 你行不行啊?  - 我行的!
- You gonna make it?  - I'm okay!
行啊你!
Nicely done!
谢谢
Thank you.
我总算没有
Finally, there's a Mrs. Hofstadter
让Hofstadter夫人失望
who isn't disappointed in me.
夜色还早
Well, the night is still young.
你还好吗?
Everything all right?
还好吧 我想
Yeah. I guess.
有事就说啊
Just tell me.
只是 在吻你的时候
It's just, when we were kissing,
我总是忍不住会脑补到你吻那个女孩的场景
I couldn't help but picture you with that other girl.
哦 不
Oh, no.
不 拜托
No, come on.
不是说好
I have a friend in you.
是好朋友吗
You said so.
说得对 当我刚才没说吧
You're right. Just forget it.
对啊
Yeah.
好吧 听着 呃
Okay, listen. Uh...
别把我和她亲吻的场景想象的很性感
If you're imagining that it was sexy.
不是的
It wasn't.
我们都喝醉了 她身上一股烟味
We... we were both drunk, and she smelled like an ashtray.
那船还摇摇晃晃的 弄得我还磕到了她牙齿
The boat was moving a lot, so I chipped her tooth.
你觉得内疚吗?
Did you feel guilty?
不会 她上了牙科保险的
No, she had dental insurance.
你吻了她觉得内疚吗
Did you feel guilty after kissing her?
当然啦 吻她那一瞬间我就觉得很内疚了
Yes. I felt guilty as soon as it happened.
到现在每一次一见到她我就觉得很内疚
I feel guilty every time I see her.
每一次见到她是什么意思?
What do you mean, every time you see her?
我... 说的话什么意思来着?
What... do I mean?
好家伙 这可真是个难题啊
Boy, that's a toughie.
你们还有联系?
You still see her?
呃 不是那种联系
Well, no, not socially.
但 你要知道 工作的时候会见到嘛
But, you know, just at work.
你和她一起工作?!
You work with her?!
为什么不告诉我?!
How could you not tell me that?!
在车里的时候我想告诉你来着 但你叫我闭嘴!
I wanted to tell you in the car, but you told me to stop talking!
哦 好吧 所以这都是我的错咯?
Oh, okay. So you're saying this is my fault?
不 当然不是了
No, of course not.
好吧 听着
Okay, look,
与其接着吵架
instead of fighting,
我们还不如把灯关了
why don't we dim the lights,
嗯 把衣服脱了然后一起造个人?
um, get naked and make a baby?
我只不过是想缓和下气氛
I was trying to lighten the mood.
很不容易的 你试试就知道了
It's not easy. You try it.
你好 母亲
Hello, Mother.
Shelly! 我的宝贝最近如何啊?
Shelly! How's my baby doing?
我只想让你知道
I just wanted to let you know
Amy可以从你的夜晚祷告名单里面除去了
that you can remove Amy from your nightly prayers.
除非你愿意帮我祈祷
Unless you're open to praying for
一个蜂窝会扣在她头上
a beehive to fall on her head.
哦 怎么了?
Oh, what's going on?
她和我分手了
She broke up with me.
哦 Shelly
Oh, Shelly.
不 我会没事的
No, I'll be okay.
不过 我觉得我可以
But I think that I'd like
把戒指寄回给您了
to send the ring back to you.
不要太着急
Well, let's not be hasty.
你确定一切都结束了吗?
Are you sure it's over for good?
我是结束了 我受够女人了
It's over for me. I'm done with women.
就像我发誓不吃跳跳糖一样
Like when I swore off Pop Rocks.
他们都是故意伤人的
They both hurt you on purpose.
可以告诉我事情的经过吗?
You want to tell me what happened?
你会说一切都是冥冥之中天注定的吗?
Are you going to say it's all part of God's plan?
很有可能
Good chance.
那算了 谢谢
Then no, thank you.
宝贝啊 先别寄回来
Well, honey, don't send it back yet.
你姐姐已经结婚了 我不想让你哥
Your sister's married, and I'm not letting your brother
把祖传戒指交给他正在交往的贱人
give my grandmother's ring to that whore he's dating.
抹大拉的马利亚（被耶稣拯救的妓女）不也名誉不佳吗?
Wasn't Mary Magdalene a woman of ill repute?
等哪天你那不开窍的哥哥拯救了人类
When your idiot brother redeems mankind,
他想和谁交往都行
he can date whoever he wants.
我知道你现在很伤心 但会好起来的
I know it hurts now, but it's gonna get better.
没错
Yeah.
一切都会好转的
Everything's gonna be okay.
你身上优点多得是
You've got so much to offer.
谢谢你
Thank you.
与你相伴是任何男人的福分
Any man would be lucky to have you.
一点没错
That's true.
我只是希望我做对了事情
I just hope I did the right thing.
那是肯定的
I'm sure you did.
或许这就是问题所在... 你一直在做对的事情
Maybe that's the problem... you always do the right thing.
或许是时候错一错了
Maybe it's time to do the wrong thing.
就像你现在这样?
Like you're doing right now?
是的
Exactly.
我一遍又一遍地问你愿不愿意
I asked you over and over if you were okay.
你既然不愿意 又何必要参加婚礼?
Why would you go through with the wedding if you weren't?
我本来觉得自己愿意 但结果并非如此
I thought I was okay, but it turns out I'm not.
好吧 听着 我可能没做到百分百的真诚
Okay, listen, I may not have been entirely faithful,
但是你 抬你真的不容易啊!
but you, you are not easy to lift!
哇哦!
Wow!
结了婚就是不一样
Well, marriage must agree with you.
你简直红光焕发啊
Well, you are just glowing.
我才没红光焕发
I'm not glowing.
我生着气呢
I'm upset.
不管是什么 你看起来很不错
Well, whatever it is, it agrees with you.
咚咚咚 Penny?
Knock, knock, knock, Penny?
咚咚咚 Penny? 咚咚咚 Penny?
Knock, knock, knock, Penny? Knock, knock, knock, Penny?
这是干什么?
What's this?
Leonard把事情告诉我了
Leonard told me what happened,
所以我就自发给你做了点热饮
so I took it upon myself to make you a hot beverage.
你真贴心啊
Oh. That's so sweet of you.
是啊 我知道
Yeah. I know.
不过 在这世道
Turns out, being sweet
单单贴心可留不住女孩
isn't enough to keep a girl these days.
暗指麦当娜的歌曲拜金女孩material girl
我觉得要怪麦当娜
I blame Madonna.
你和Amy分手的事真是可惜
I'm sorry to hear about you and Amy.
关于Leonard 也是可惜
Well, I'm sorry about Leonard.
我以为自己已经把他调教好了
Thought I raised him better than that.
本来这事就够糟糕了
You know, it's bad enough what happened,
他还试图隐瞒他每天
but then he tried to hide the fact that he sees her
都在学校里看见她的事实
all the time at the university.
每天都见? 是谁啊?
He does? Who is it?
一个叫Mandy的女孩
Some girl named Mandy.
- Mandy Chao?  - 就这货
- Mandy Chao?  - Yeah.
你没必要担心人家啦
Oh, you don't need to worry about her.
她智慧和美丽兼具
She's brilliant and attractive.
她才看不上Leonard呢
She can do way better than Leonard.
真好啊
That's great.
等一等
Wait a minute.
我知道这听起来有点不靠谱
I know this may sound farfetched,
但我现在单身待售呢
but I'm on the market now.
我要是跟Mandy约会
You know, if I dated Mandy,
算是同时给Leonard和Amy一个教训
that would teach both Leonard and Amy a lesson.
太荒谬了
That's ridiculous.
嗯 你说得对 我不能跟一个自尊心低到
Oh, you're right. I could never be with a woman
跟Leonard约会的人在一起
whose self-esteem was so low she'd be with Leonard.
我跟Leonard在一起呢
I'm with Leonard.
嗯 我知道 回不了头了
Yeah, I know. Forever.
真想不到会走到今天这一步？
Who would have believed these things would happen to us?
对吧？
Right?
不敢相信Amy真的说到做到了
I can't believe Amy actually went through with it.
等下
Hang on.
你早就知道她要跟我分手？
You knew that she was going to end it with me?
你有试着阻止她吗？
Did you try and stop her?
我告诉她听从自己的想法做让她开心的事
I told her to be true to herself and do what makes her happy.
做让她开心的事？
Do what makes her happy?
她会弹竖琴 而且车付了全款
She plays the harp and her car is paid for.
她还想要多快乐？
How much happier can she be?
好吧 听着 她觉得你是个糟糕的男友
Okay, look, it's not my fault
不是我的错
that she thought you were a bad boyfriend.
我懂了
I see.
好吧...
Well...
我要走了
I think I'll be going.
- Sheldon...  - 别说话
- Sheldon...  - No, no, no, no.
我们谈完了
We are done here.
你能不能打开门
Would you mind opening the door
然后非常生气地在我背后关上？
and then angrily slamming it behind me?
当然
Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
注意摔狠点
And slam it hard,
因为我非常生气
because I am pretty steamed.
好吧 Leonard 别伤心
All right, Leonard, hang in there.
明天见
Talk to you tomorrow.
怎么了？ 他们才刚结婚
What happened? They just got married.
我不知道
I don't know.
乱七八糟的 他们在维加斯大吵了一架
It's a mess. They had a huge fight in Vegas.
你觉得他们会分手吗？
Think they'll break up?
不晓得 听着挺糟糕的
I don't know. Sounds pretty bad.
Penny一个人搬回她公寓了
Penny's back in her apartment all by herself.
是咩？
Really?
你想不想再听一个
Would you like to hear another reason
男人比女人好的原因？
why men are better than women?
当然 凑齐一百个吧
Sure, let's make it an even hundred.
你绝对不会吻我 然后让我说"我爱你"
You would never kiss me and make me say "I love you"
然后跟我分手
and then break up with me.
我确实不会
I wouldn't.
你知道为什么吗？
And you know why?
因为你是个男人
'Cause you're a man.
性别里的香槟酒
The champagne of genders.
我虽然是个男人
Well, I may be a man,
但我觉得这次是我把事情搞砸了
but I think I'm the one that screwed up on this one.
好吧 但你承认了 像个男人一样
Yeah, well, and you admit it, like a man.
女人们就只会说
All you hear women say is,
"我点个沙拉就好" 对不?
"I'll just have a salad." You know?
"我的润唇膏呢？"
"Where's my lip gloss?"
"我觉得这个元素应该叫镭"
"I think this element should be called radium."
最后一个是居里夫人
That last one was Madame Curie.
我猜出来了
I figured that out.
你知道吗？ 她算是名义上的男人
You know what? She was kind of an honorary man.
科学给了她男人的家伙
She had a penis made of science.
真不敢相信我新婚夜是跟你过的
Can't believe I'm spending my wedding night with you.
是吗？
Really?
这一直是我预料的结果
I never imagined it any other way.